(
"ai_sub_version": "3.3.0",
"generated_at": "2026-07-17T23:43:33.624580",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
音乃瀬奏生誕祭2026「Rise in motion」
[Standby Screen: Otonose Kanade Birthday Livestream 2026 "Rise in motion"]
えー、みなちゃま！
Uh, everyone!
本日は「音乃瀬奏生誕祭2026 Rise in motion」にお越しくださいまして
Thank you so much for coming to Otonose Kanade's
Birthday Festival 2026 "Rise in motion" today...
誠にありがとうございます！
...thank you very much!
えー、開演に先立ちまして、みなちゃまにお願いとご案内を申し上げます。
Prior to the start of the performance, I would
like to make some requests and announcements to everyone.
えー、当配信は一部収録を含みますが、生配信部分もございますので、いっぱいコメントして盛り上げてください！
This stream includes some pre-recorded parts,
but there are also live stream parts, so please comment a lot and let's get hyped!
今もね、ぶわーって、いっぱい、おお、こんちくわ、きたー、パチパチと、ありがとうございます！
Right now, I see lots of comments like "Hello,"
"Here we go!" and clapping emojis flowing in. Thank you!
えー、当配信のハッシュタグは、「#音乃瀬奏生誕祭2026」です。
The hashtag for this stream is
"#OtonoseKanadeBirthday2026."
SNSでたくさんポストしていただけると嬉しいです。
We would be very happy if you could
post a lot on social media.
えー、開演中はね、カメラやスマートフォンなどによる写真撮影大歓迎なので、たくさんポストして盛り上げていただけると幸いです。
Taking photos with cameras or smartphones is highly welcome during the show,
so we hope you post many of them and keep the hype going!
えー、それでは、開演までしばらくお待ちください！
Well then, please wait a little longer until
the show starts!
えー、みなちゃま！
Uh, everyone!
本日は「音乃瀬奏生誕祭2026 Rise in motion」にお越しくださいまして
Thank you so much for coming to Otonose Kanade's
Birthday Festival 2026 "Rise in motion" today...
誠にありがとうございます、パート2！
...thank you very much! Part 2!
どれどれ？なんか、ぐだぐだしてなさそうですね、みなちゃん。
Let's see... looks like you all aren't
getting too restless, everyone.
おおーって、わくわく、こんちくわと。だ、大丈夫そうです！
I see comments like "Oooh," "Excited,"
and "Hello." Looks like everything is going great!
えー、開演に先立ちまして、みなちゃまにお願いとご案内を、ちょっともう一回申し上げます。
Prior to the start, let me make the requests
and announcements to everyone once again.
えー、当配信は一部収録を含みますが、生配信部分もございますので、いっぱいコメントして盛り上げていただけると嬉しいです。
This stream includes some pre-recorded parts,
but there are also live stream parts, so we would be happy if you commented a lot to build up the excitement.
きちゃ！大丈夫ちょ？パート2！きちゃ！ありがとう！
You're here! Are you okay? Part 2! You're here! Thank you!
えー、今日配信のハッシュタグは、ハッシュタグ「おとはしの生誕祭2026」です！
Uh, today's stream hashtag is hashtag #OtohashiBirthdayCelebration2026!
SNSでたくさんポストしてください！
Please post a lot on SNS!
えー、公演中は、カメラやスマートフォンなどによる写真撮影大歓迎です！
Uh, during the performance, taking photos with cameras or smartphones is highly welcome!
たくさんポストして、盛り上げていただけると嬉しいです！
I'd be happy if you post a lot and hype things up!
それでは、開演まで、今しばらく、お待ちください！
Now then, please wait a little longer until the show begins!
STAR AUDITION COME AND JOIN
ふっ
Huh!
バンザイ 無能な命に
Cheers to an incompetent life,
くだらないよ 紛い物だって ボラリアップ
It's worthless, even if it's a sham... volaliup!
BANZAI
作詞・作曲：マサ 編曲：田中タツヤ
[Title: BANZAI]
Lyrics & Composition: Masa / Arrangement: Tatsuya Tanaka
喝采 消し去るようなもん
An ovation is something that fades away,
不条理 浴びながら 僕は home
Bathed in absurdity, I'm home.
才能はゼロ
Talent is zero,
どうにかなりちまっちゃってるけど
Though somehow it's all gone wrong,
歓声は no だっての
The cheers are a "no", because...
愛にもたされた言葉で心拍数
Heartbeat driven by words leaned on love,
生きていく程 胸は沈んでいく
The more I live, the more my heart sinks.
どうなってんだろ？なあ
What's going on, huh?
この音が 揺れるの
Is this sound shaking?
かい摘んでもしょうがねぇ
There's no point in summarizing it.
汗かき稼ぐお金はどんだけ？
How much money earned from sweating?
あーだこーだ そんなもんか
This and that, is that all?
五月蝿いわ なあ
Shut up, will you?
バンザイ 無能な命に
Cheers to an incompetent life,
から回ってく脳を満たしてくれ
Fill my brain that's spinning in vain.
未来予想図なんか描けない
I can't draw any blueprint for the future,
くだらないよ 紛い物だって それ
It's worthless, even if it's a sham.
半端者ならやれない nutty tune
A half-baked person couldn't pull off this nutty tune,
朱色になって 僕は思い通り
Turning vermilion, I get my way.
太陽系で巣食う また罵詈雑言インベーダー
Nesting in the solar system, yet another abusive-tongued invader.
足が止まってるシューゲイザー 死にそうでもギリですか？
A shoegazer whose feet have stopped, is this barely making it even if about to die?
のらりくらり躱すわ
I'll dodge it lazily.
初めまして カミサマ
Nice to meet you, God.
もし救われるのなら
If I'm to be saved,
腹切るわ 今から
I'll commit hara-kiri right now.
get down 揺らめく
Get down, wavering,
get down 飲み込んだ清濁が
Get down, the good and evil I swallowed...
君を狂わしてんだ
...are driving you crazy!
めったなもんじゃおどろかねぇ
I won't be easily surprised.
汗かき生きた最期もあっけねぇ
Even the end of a life spent sweating is so anticlimactic.
なんだかんだ そんなもんさ
One way or another, that's just how it is.
虚しいわ なあ
It's empty, isn't it?
バンザイ 無能な...
Cheers to an incompetent...
エナジー 絡まって
Energy, getting tangled up
テクノを満たしてくれ
Fill me with techno
未来予想図なんか描けない
I can't even draw a future blueprint
くだらない夢 買い戻したってそれ
Even if I buy back a worthless dream
半端者なら やれない
If you're half-hearted, you can't do it
マネージャー！
Manager!
お代わりになって ボスは思う通り
Become a replacement, just as the boss wants
足りらりら 此処は何処？ きっと奈落の底
Tarirarira, where is this? Surely at the bottom of hell
声にもならん呪詛が
A curse that cannot even be voiced...
腹の底から競り上がるんだ
...rises up from the bottom of my stomach.
ダサいその愛 押し殺す本能
That uncool love, the instinct to suppress it
ゆらゆら にび色の海と揺れましょう
Swaying back and forth, let's sway with the dark-gray sea
ただただ君は呟くんだ
You just mumble softly,
人は 永遠に
"Humans are eternal."
今、弾ける桃色
Now, bursting into pink
はい、はい、はい、宙を舞って踊り散らすの
Yes, yes, yes, dancing wildly in the air
ファッションビートで気気取って
Showing off with a fashion beat
地味キャラ？狂人じゃない
A plain character? I'm not a madman!
救われない悲しみ喰らってこう
Let's feast on the unsaved sadness
ファッションビートに染まって
Dyed in the fashion beat
言うことないなら息引き取っても無駄だ
If you have nothing to say, breathing is a waste anyway
はい、はい、はい、はい、悪辣少年よ
Yes, yes, yes, yes, villainous boy!
ええじゃないか ええじゃないか
Isn't it fine? Isn't it fine?
この先は何も分からんし
We don't know anything about what lies ahead anyway
ええじゃないか ええじゃないか
Isn't it fine? Isn't it fine?
糞垂れ見てなれ 煩脳
Look at that piece of crap, worldly desires
荒れ狂う 世の中の馬鹿らから
From the fools of this raging world,
はい、はい、はい、はい、宙を舞って踊り散らすの
yes, yes, yes, yes, dancing wildly in the air
ファッションビートで気取って
Showing off with a fashion beat
地味キャラ？狂人じゃない
A plain character? I'm not a madman!
救われない悲しみ喰らってこう
Let's feast on the unsaved sadness
ファッションビートに染まって
Dyed in the fashion beat
言うことないなら息引き取っても無駄だ
If you have nothing to say, breathing is a waste anyway
はい、はい、はい、はい、悪辣少年よ
Yes, yes, yes, yes, villainous boy!
あの日描いたようなストーリー 僕の色
The kind of story I drew that day, my color
濡れた歩道に落ち込んでた
I was feeling down on the wet sidewalk
モノクロに過ぎる日は
The days that pass in monochrome...
乗り越えられたら
...if I could overcome them...
あぁ、今夜は笑って あの幽霊車にキッスをして
Ah, smile tonight, and kiss that ghost train
七色に生まれ変わるのさ
I will be reborn in seven colors
ファッションビートに染まって
Dyed in the fashion beat
言うことないなら息引き取っても無駄だ
If you have nothing to say, breathing is a waste anyway
はい、はい、はい、はい、悪辣少年よ
Yes, yes, yes, yes, villainous boy!
はぁー！楽しい！
Phew! That was fun!
やっぱり、歌って踊るの楽しい！
Singing and dancing is definitely the best!
イェーイ！イェーイ！
Yay! Yay!
いや、ちょっとぶちかましちゃったんですけど、どうでした？
Well, I kind of went all out. How was it?
え、なんか「番長」とかやってたんですか？
Wait, was there some "Bancho" thing going on?
え？お？なん、なん、なんですか？
Eh? Oh? What, what is it?
え、なんか撮ってました？
Wait, were you recording?
え、なんか撮ってましたよね？
Wait, you were recording, right?
え、てか、なんかこれ配置... これ配置されてます、これ！
Wait, is this layout... this layout is already set up, isn't it?!
えー！？
What?!
ちょっと待って、これ勝手にとかあるんですけど、はじめにも！
Wait a minute, this is being done without my permission from the very start!
な、な、コメントがすごい流れてるんですけど...
The- The comments are scrolling like crazy...
反転してて読めません！
They're mirrored, so I can't read them!
えっと、なんか、パチパチって拍手してくれてて...
Um, people are clapping for me...
なんか「かっこよすぎ」って...なに？
They're saying "way too cool"... what?
え、すごいなんか、え、草？草？なんか草生やされた。え、なんか...
Eh, wow, somehow... wait, "lol"? I got spammed with "lol". Eh, what...
なんか、ありがとうございました。
Anyway, thank you very much!
ハッシュタグ、「#轟はじめ生誕祭2026」で、なんかたくさんぽちぽちしてくれてるみたいなんですけど...
It looks like many people are tweeting with the hashtag "#TodorokiHajimeBirthday2026"...
なんだろう、このタグ。わからないけど...
I wonder what this tag is. I don't know, but...
はじめ、祝ってもらえてるし、ぽちぽちしてもらえたら嬉しいかも！
Hajime is being celebrated, so I'd be happy if you tweeted!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
えっと、はじめ、歌ったり踊ったりするの好きで...
Um, Hajime likes singing and dancing...
本当はこう、たくさんの人の前でパフォーマンスすることに憧れて、ちょっと上京したいな、とか思ってるんですけど...
Actually, I've always dreamed of performing in front of lots of people and wanted to move to Tokyo...
ちょっと勇気が出なくて...
But I just couldn't build up the courage...
うわ、え？
Whoa, eh?
「はじめなら大丈夫」？「いける」？
"Hajime will be fine"? "You can do it"?
え、コメントの方はちょっとどう思ってる？
Eh, what do you guys in the comments think?
「かわいい」「なんて？」あ、ダンスうま！すごい褒められてる！
"Cute", "What?" Ah, "Great dancing!" Wow, I'm getting praised!
あ、かっこいい！褒められてる！
Ah, "Cool!" I'm being praised!
よし！じゃあみんなにすごい勇気をもらったので、はじめ...
Alright! Since everyone gave me so much courage, Hajime...
行ってきます！夢を目指して、上京してくる！
Is off! I'm moving to Tokyo to pursue my dream!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
荒れ狂う季節の中を
In the rampaging seasons,
二人は一人きり さらり
together but all alone, easily...
明け行く夕日の中を
In the dawning sunset,
今夜も昼下がり さらり
tonight as well in the early afternoon, easily.
どれほど朽ち果てようと
No matter how much I rot away,
最後には笑いたい
I wanna laugh in the end...
何のために
For what purpose?
戦おうとも 動機は愛がいい あぁ
Whatever you fight for, your motive should be love, ah.
新しい日々は 探さずとも常に
Even if you don't look for them, new days are always...
ここに (ここに)
here (right here).
色々見てきたけれど
I've seen many things, but
この瞳は永遠に きらり
these eyes of mine are forever shining.
あれほど生きてきたけれど
I've lived so much, but
全ては夢みたい
everything's like a dream.
あれもこれも
This and that...
魅力的なのも 私は君がいい あぁ
are attractive, but I want you, ah.
どこにいたの 探してたよ
Where'd you go? I searched for you...
連れてって 連れてって
Take me with you, take me with you.
何もかも 捨ててくよ
I'll abandon everything...
どこまでも どこまでも
Anywhere, anywhere!
荒れ狂う季節の中も 群衆の中も
In the rampaging seasons, in the throng,
君とならば さらり さらり
as long as I'm with you, then so easily, so easily.
新しい日々も 拙い過去も 全てがきらり
New days and a shoddy past are all shining...
なくしてしまったものを振り返って
Reflect on what you've lost...
ほろり
sentimental.
時には途方に暮れて ただ風に吹かれて
At times at a loss, blowin' in the wind...
ゆらり
swaying.
息せき切ってきたの
I was out of breath...
行き先は決めたの
I've decided my destination.
迷わずにいきたいけれど 保証はしないよ
I wanna go without hesitating, but I can't make any guarantees.
何か分かったようで 何も分かってなくて
Like I've figured something out, but don't know anything.
あなたと出会えて本当によかった
I'm so glad I met you.
新しい日々は探さずとも
Even if I don't look for new days,
常にここに
they are always right here,
always right here,
ここに
right here,
ここに ある
right here they are.
色々見てきたけれど
I've seen many things, but
この瞳は永遠に君を
these eyes will forever look at you
永遠にキラリ
and forever shine.
生きてきたけれど全ては夢みたい
I've been living, but everything is like a dream.
あれもこれも 魅力的でも
Even though this and that are appealing,
私は君がいい
you're the one for me.
どこに行ったの
Where did you go?
探していたよ
I was looking for you.
連れてって
Take me,
take me with you.
何もかも捨てていくよ
I'll cast everything aside,
どこまでも
anywhere,
wherever.
荒れ狂う季節の中も
Even through the raging seasons,
群衆の中も
and through the crowds,
君とならばさらりさらり
with you, it's so effortless.
新しい日々も拙い過去も
The new days, the clumsy past,
全てがきらり
everything is shining.
ほら、踊れば
Look, if we dance,
幕開けの合図が
the signal for the curtain rise
It's coming back
is coming back.
月火から水木金
From Mon, Tue to Wed, Thu, Fri,
お疲れ Everybody clap your hands
good job, everybody clap your hands.
待ちわびた金土日
The long-awaited Fri, Sat, Sun,
さぁ Come on, bring all your friends
now come on, bring all your friends.
世間はワクワク 目線はソワソワ
The world is excited, eyes are restless,
心も体もボロボロです
my heart and body are worn out.
頑張り屋な日本人に
To the hard-working Japanese people,
Everybody clap your hands
やるせない Yesterday
Miserable yesterday,
うんざりしちゃって
I'm so sick of it.
何もかも Night routine
Everything is a night routine,
染み込んだクセ
an ingrained habit.
他人のせい？ また自分のせい？
Is it others' fault? Or my own fault again?
憧れ持ったのあの日で
The day I held admiration,
結局はいつも通りだ
in the end, it's just business as usual.
過ぎ去っていく Day by day
Day by day, passing us by,
考えたって There's no best life way
even if we think, there's no best way of life.
僕らノイズも味方にして Let's run away
Let's make even our noise our ally and run away.
Welcome to our Theater
ほら 踊れば
Look, if we dance,
幕開けの合図が It's coming back
the signal for the curtain rise is coming back.
波瀾万丈な人生くらいが
A life full of ups and downs
ちょうどいいのさ
is just about right.
君が創る Showtime
The showtime you create,
見せて 見せて 頂戴
show me, please show it to me.
春夏秋冬に
Through spring, summer, fall, winter,
あれあれ Everybody clap your hands
oh my, everybody clap your hands.
ギリギリ駆け込んで間に合うか？
Rushing in at the last second, will we make it?
これが Ending game
This is the ending game.
気持ちは Go-go されども No-no
Our feelings say go-go, but we say no-no;
現実はそう甘くないね
reality isn't that sweet.
働き者な日本人に
To the hard-working Japanese people,
Everybody clap your hands
お決まりのルーティン代
The usual routine's price,
How can I live my life myself, oh my
どれもこれも色のない世界に興味ない
I'm not interested in any colorless world.
僕らノイズも
Even our noise,
味方にして Let's run away
make it our ally, and let's run away.
Welcome to our Theater
ほら 踊れば
Look, if we dance,
幕開けの合図が It's coming back
the signal for the curtain rise is coming back.
波瀾万丈な人生くらいが
A life full of ups and downs
ちょうどいいのさ
is just about right.
君が創る Showtime
The showtime you create,
見せて 見せて
show me, show me...
過ぎ去っていく Day by day
Day by day, passing us by,
考えたって There's no best life way
even if we think, there's no best way of life.
僕らノイズも味方にして Let's run away
Let's make even our noise our ally and run away.
Welcome to our Theater
ほら 踊れば
Look, if we dance,
幕開けの合図が It's coming back
the signal for the curtain rise is coming back.
波瀾万丈な人生くらいが
A life full of ups and downs
ちょうどいいのさ
is just about right.
君が創る Showtime
The showtime you create,
見せて 見せて 頂戴
show me, please show it to me.
とびきり Showtime
An extraordinary showtime,
誰でも Showtime
showtime for anyone,
あなたの Showtime を見せて頂戴
show me your showtime, please.
とびきり Showtime
An extraordinary showtime,
誰でも Showtime
showtime for anyone,
あなたの Showtime を見せて頂戴
show me your showtime, please.
えっ？何？星街すいせいのチャンネルにしようにゃ
Eh? What? Let's make it Hoshimachi Suisei's channel, nya!
ご存知かしら？ありがとう！
Do you know of it? Thank you!
えっ何？なんか超偶然でできたけど
Eh, what? It happened completely by chance, but...
すいちゃんと一緒に歌えて嬉しかったでしゅ
I was so happy to sing with you, Sui-chan!
私も嬉しかったわ
I was happy too.
わあ、嬉しい！すいちゃん、ありがとう！
Wow, I'm so happy! Thank you, Sui-chan!
えっ、でも、でも、このシアター、勝手に入っていいんですか？
Wait, but... is it really okay for us to just walk into this theater?
まあ、ダメかもしれないわ
Well, maybe we shouldn't have.
ダメなの！？えっ、じゃあ怒られる？これ
We shouldn't!? Wait, will we get in trouble for this?
え、じゃあ怒られる、これ
Wait, so we will get in trouble?
まあ怒られるわ
Well, yeah. We definitely will.
なんでここ連れてきてくれたんですか！
Then why did you bring me here?!
あそこの人がもう銃構えてるわ、こうやって
Look, that person over there is already aiming a gun like this...
怖い怖い怖い！そんな物騒なもの持ってますか？
Scary, scary, scary! Are they holding something that dangerous?!
あ、違う違う。あの、この人オーディション、オーディション出場者でしょ、え？
Oh, no, wait. That person is... an audition contestant, right? Huh?
えっ？
Huh?
ここでオーディションやってるんで、オーディション出場者、今年。ね？
They are holding auditions here, so they're a contestant this year. Right?
ってことは...
Which means...
ここでオーディションやってたんだ
They were holding auditions here.
そうだよ。受けた方がいいんじゃない？ねえ、立ち向かう
Yes. Shouldn't you audition too? You know, stand up to them.
じゃないと撃たれる、撃たれる
Otherwise you'll get shot, you'll get shot!
怖い、怖いよ！
Scary, that's scary!
あれ、星街すいせいじゃない！？
Hey, isn't that Hoshimachi Suisei!?
い、いけね！じゃーね！
O-Oh crap! See ya!
えっ！？ちょっと、ちょっと！やばい！ええー！？
Huh!? Wait, wait! This is bad! Eh!?
ありゃ？ええー？どっちや？あー...
Huh? What? Which way? Ah...
しーっ
Shh...
ステップはお静かに
[Title: Steps Quietly]
Steal like a spy, toe-ing 踊るパーティパーティタイム
Steal like a spy, toe-ing, dancing in the party party time
抜き足 差し足 忍び行く劇場
Tiptoeing stealthily, slipping into the theater
Step by step behind... 教えるわ
Step by step behind... I'll show you how
心の思うまま 踊るステップステップで
Just as your heart desires, dancing step-by-step
強気な瞳 隠して
Hiding those confident eyes
少しだけ 少しだけ 笑って
With just a little, little smile
上品なキック 蹴り上げ
Kicking up an elegant high kick
静かに ちょっと豪快に
Quietly, and a little dynamically
仕留めてあげるわ決まりよ
I'll finish you off
Step like... 同じダンス ばっかりじゃ駄目
Step like... just doing the same dance won't do
Feel like... もう一人の自分に勝つの
Feel like... overcoming another version of myself
だって 盗まれたら 取り返すのが基本でしょ
After all, if it's stolen, taking it back is only basic
Tap tap eyes spies... 静かに足音
Tap tap eyes spies... with quiet footsteps
ひらりとかわしていくのよ
Dodging nimbly out of the way
すらりと手には勝機じゃん
Smoothly, victory is in my hands
華麗に無音で逃げ切る
Making a clean escape in splendid silence
静かに ちょっと豪快に
Quietly, and a little dynamically
仕留めてあげるわ決まりよ
I'll finish you off
Step like... 奪い返し パーティパーティタイム
Step like... taking it back, party party time
抜き足 差し足 忍び行く劇場
Tiptoeing stealthily, slipping into the theater
Step by step behind... そのまま踊ってね
Step by step behind... keep dancing just like that
ずっと付いてきてよね
Make sure to keep up with me
踏み出してみてよ
Take a step forward
ここで決めるの
I'll decide it right here
誰も奪わせないわ
I won't let anyone steal it
胸に秘めてる法則を
With the laws hidden inside my chest
静かに踊って
Dance quietly
静かに踊るよ
I will dance quietly
ステップはお静かに
Keep the steps quiet
BAD HATTER
[Title: BAD HATTER]
sweetie night に mary jane
sweetie night to mary jane
かかと カンカン tap する 伽藍 堂
heels furiously tap in the temple hall
secret sign ほら ご 招待
hey, look, secret sign invitation
超お洒落で小癪な説教などナビゲート
Navigating through hyper-fashionable and cheeky preachiness...
Step inside 今夜はLunatic
Step inside, tonight is Lunatic.
既に昂揚 終生 執着に Grab your souls
Already exhilarated, grabbing your souls with lifelong obsession.
さぁ乾杯してディベロップジェン 今はこの欲に溺れよう
Now, let's raise a toast and drown in this desire.
有限なら夜が明ける前までに
Since life is finite, before the dawn breaks...
味わい尽くすべき
...we should taste it all.
You are BAD HATTER 親愛なるモンスター
You are BAD HATTER, my dear monster.
We are BAD HATTER 酩酊も対象もナンセンス
We are BAD HATTER, both drunkenness and symmetry are nonsense.
Bam-Bam Moonlight 渋滞のダンスフロア
Bam-Bam Moonlight on the congested dance floor.
We are stakeholder 狂騒に呑まれ踊れ
We are stakeholders, swallowed by the frenzy, so dance!
脱知性的deviation 常に空中飛び交う狂言ドーム
Anti-intellectual deviation, dynamic farces flying through the air.
甲斐性無いなら平等さ 老いも若きも目眩し飾り合う
If you have no talent, we're all equal; young and old dazzle and dress up.
Step inside 今夜はLunatic 誰彼もが耳打ちクレイジートーク
Step inside, tonight is Lunatic, everyone whispering crazy talk.
一緒にどうですお嬢さん 素性を隠した紳士がShall we dance?
How about joining us, miss? A gentleman in disguise asks, "Shall we dance?"
有象無象 どんな見た目だろうが
Riff-raff, no matter what you look like...
気にする暇もない
...there's no time to care.
You are BAD HATTER 親愛なるモンスター
You are BAD HATTER, my dear monster.
We are BAD HATTER 酩酊も対象もナンセンス
We are BAD HATTER, both drunkenness and symmetry are nonsense.
Bam-Bam Moonlight 渋滞のダンスフロア
Bam-Bam Moonlight on the congested dance floor.
We are stakeholder 狂騒に呑まれ踊れ
We are stakeholders, swallowed by the frenzy, so dance!
ダバデュバダビディディ...
Daba duba dabi di di...
ドゥダディビディビドゥドゥディディディドゥ
Du da dibi dibi du du di di di du...
デュビダバドゥギャドゥダドゥブダビディダドゥダディビドゥ
Dubi daba du gya du da dubu dabi di da du da dibi du...
ダブダブダブダブダブドゥダラダブダブダブダブダバドゥ
Dabu dabu dabu dabu dabu du dara dabu dabu dabu dabu daba du...
アビバリドゥダラドゥダラディバジュバディダドゥダディビディバビディドゥ
Abibari du dara du dara dibajuba di da du da dibidi babidi du.
You are BAD HATTER 親愛なるモンスター
You are BAD HATTER, my dear monster.
We are BAD HATTER 酩酊も対象もナンセンス
We are BAD HATTER, both drunkenness and symmetry are nonsense.
Bam-Bam Moonlight 渋滞のダンスフロア
Bam-Bam Moonlight on the congested dance floor.
We are stakeholder 狂騒に呑まれ踊れ
We are stakeholders, swallowed by the frenzy, so dance!
うわっ！まいちきおるやん！
Whoa! Maichiki is here!
何持ってるの？
What are you holding?
お？
Oh?
バツ？
An X?
バツってどういうこと？も、もしかして...
What do you mean by "X"? Could it be...
おはしちゃんの審査員だったの？
...you were Ohashi-chan's judge?!
え、だってさっき、なんかノリノリで「ダバデュバダビディディ」ってやってたじゃん！
But earlier, you were grooving and going "daba duba dabi di di"!
え？どいてって？
Huh? "Move aside"?
なんなんだよ！
What the heck!
おはし頑張って踊ったのに...
Ohashi worked so hard to dance...
え、ちょっと、ちょっとどいてって...
Wait, "move aside"?
ねぇ！
Hey!
あれ？
Huh?
なんかガチで動かないんだけど...
I seriously can't move...
あ、なんか話しかけてもダメみたいだ...
Ah, seems like talking to them won't work either...
なんだよ！こっちから願い下げだ！
Fine then! I wouldn't want it anyway!
こんなシアター、出てってやる！
I'm leaving this theater!
なんなんだよ、もう！
What is up with that, seriously!
あいつら何なんだよ！
Who do they think they are?!
並んでるしよ！
And they're all lined up!
並ぶな！
Don't line up!
並んでんじゃねぇ！
Stop lining up!
あぁ...最悪...
Ah... This is the worst...
脳内狂 ALL RIGHT
Brain's going crazy, but ALL RIGHT.
能天気 如何様 STAY
Carefree, staying fake.
お節介 説教して 機嫌を正していれ
Meddling and preaching, keeping them in good humor.
精神的 HOLD ON
Mental HOLD ON.
ミステイクス 崩壊している
Mistakes are collapsing.
真偽不明な伝承 正気じゃない
Unverifiable lore, it's insane.
夜は オン オン オン オン
The night is on, on, on, on.
僕ら オン オン オン オン
We are on, on, on, on.
手招きを頂戴
Beckon me, please.
針は針はコン・コン・コン・コン
The clock hands go tick-tock, tick-tock.
吸って吐いてジャッジメント
Inhale, exhale, judgment.
容赦困難 ブレイコー 決定です
No mercy, let's break rules, it's decided!
皆サマ ナンセンス
Everyone, it's nonsense.
甚だナンセンス
Extremely nonsense.
呆れる流れ
A shocking turn of events.
黙れ！黙れ！
Shut up! Shut up!
この世はナンセンス
This world is nonsense.
誠にカンバス
Truly a canvas.
気の毒ね
How pitiful.
暴れ！暴れ！仕方ねぇ！
Rampage! Rampage! Can't be helped!
ほら正正堂堂
Look, fair and square...
一人一人討ち取っちゃうぞ
...I'll defeat you one by one!
閻魔によろしく言っといて！
Say hello to King Enma for me!
BE QUIET, ALL RIGHT
画期的な STAY
A revolutionary STAY.
名義不明だとしても参りたい
Even if anonymous, I want to join.
夜にカーテンコール
Curtain call for the night.
まさに千客万来
Indeed, it's a massive crowd!
だって party night
Because it's party night!
右も左も どんとはらい
Left and right, that is all!
フッて湧いた チェックメイト
An unexpected checkmate!
ようやく今晩 ブレイコー 決行です
Tonight, the wild party is finally on!
皆様 ナンセンス はなはだ ナンセンス
To everyone, it's nonsense, utter nonsense!
聞き流せ 黙れ 黙れ 黙れ
Just ignore it, shut up, shut up, shut up!
この世は ナンセンス 誠に 遺憾です
This world is nonsense, it's truly regrettable!
お気の毒ね 暴れ 暴れ 暴れ
What a pity! Go wild, go wild, go wild!
Can't you understand?
Yeah yeah yeah yeah...
皆様 ナンセンス はなはだ ナンセンス
To everyone, it's nonsense, utter nonsense!
聞き流せ 黙れ 黙れ 黙れ
Just ignore it, shut up, shut up, shut up!
この世は ナンセンス はなから ナンセンス
This world is nonsense, nonsense from the start!
聞き流せ 黙れ 黙れ 黙れ
Just ignore it, shut up, shut up, shut up!
まもなく 時間です 誠に 遺憾です
Time is almost up, it's truly regrettable!
お気は済んだ？ 下がれ 下がれ くたばれ
Had your fun? Step back, step back, drop dead!
ほら精神牙剥いていってらっしゃい
Now, bare your fangs and off you go!
肥大調子づいちゃってヒィカラ
Getting cocky and running on empty...
Ｓ・Ｒ・Ｉ・Ｐ・Ｐで御免被る
Pardon me with an S-R-I-P-P!
終電で来世に会おう See you again
Let's meet in the next life on the last train, see you again!
うおーっ！びっくりした、あぶにゃ！
Whoa! You startled me, that was close!
危ないんじゃないですか？
Isn't that dangerous?
え？何ちゅうその動き。お前、ダンサー？
Eh? What's with those moves? Are you a dancer?
え、ダンサーですけど。
Eh, yeah, I'm a dancer.
え、私も！
Eh, me too!
私もダンサーです！
I'm a dancer too!
え、なんかすごいダンサーがいっぱい出てきた。
Whoa, suddenly a bunch of dancers appeared!
え、ちょいちょい、なんかさ、はじめちゃん、ダンサーのオーディション落ちちゃってさ...
Wait, wait, actually, Hajime-chan failed a dancer audition...
もしかして、あそこのシアターですか？
Could it be the theater over there?
え、そう！
Ah, yes!
え、それ私も落ちました！
Eh, I failed that too!
えー！私も！私も私も！
What?! Me too! Me too, me too!
え、みんな落ちた仲間？！
Wait, we're all fellow failures?!
うん！ねー！
Yeah! Exactly!
あの審査員、センス無いよねー！
Those judges have zero taste!
そうそう！本当に！
Totally! For real!
いやいや、うちらのダンス、ちゃんと見せつけてやろうじゃ！
Well then, let's show them what our dance is really about!
おー！
Yeah!
もう壁とは踊らないぞ、インセキュアな自分にサヨナラ！
No more dancing with walls, goodbye to my insecure self...
3メートルの覇気、水を得る！
3-meter conqueror's haki, like fish to water!
カオスに落ちるハコス・ベールズ！
Falling into chaos, Hakos Baelz!
宇宙一の番長になる、轟はじめ！
To become the universe's number one bancho, Todoroki Hajime!
よし、うちらの始まりは...
Alright, our beginning is...
こっから！
From here!
Yeah! Hey boy! Ordinary boring Japan
産ぶ声をおぎゃ 行く先はこや
First cry ogya, the destination is a hut,
呑まれるいかがいかがにして 深く深く眠る魂をほれ呼び起こすか
how to be swallowed. Will you wake up the soul sleeping deep underground?
知るか乗るか反るかしかめっ面 世の中確かめたい価値観のドブ価値観
Do you know? In this world, take it or not, are certain values worthless?
となんだってこの葛藤で 生まれたての剥き出しの規格外のギア
Even with this conflict, a newborn, raw, non-standard gear is here.
I can't summarize so I know, I know
このブレーキを壊したいの、したいの
I want to break this brake, I want to.
これだけじゃやれねえって分かってる でもこれしかねえからこれにかかってる 間違ってる未来でも俺には光ってる Let it fire!
I know I can't do this alone, but this is all I have, so everything depends on this. Even in a wrong future, it shines for me. Let it fire!
燃やす闘志 その手少し ぶっ壊し通しようもないままが自分なんだ
Burning this fighting spirit, breaking it all, my helpless self is who I am!
Get up, stand up, こっから始まんだ
Get up, stand up, it starts from here!
いつかの闘志 持って少し 夢と添い遂げられるはずなんだ
Carrying that old fighting spirit, I should be able to live out my dreams.
Get up, stand up, こっから、こっから始まんだ
Get up, stand up, it starts from here, right here!
1 2 3 4 順番通り
1 2 3 4, in order,
言ってないだけで予定通り
just as planned, even if I didn't say so.
Rollin' Rollin' 転がっていけ
Rollin', rollin', let's roll away!
よりどり緑の一生
A life full of endless choices.
1 2 3 4 順番通り
1 2 3 4, in order,
言ってないだけで予定通り
just as planned, even if I didn't say so.
Rollin' Rollin' 転がっていこう こっから始まんだ
Rollin', rollin', let's roll away! It starts from here.
え、こっからどっからわからんだって 燃料切れならすっからかん
Ayy, I don't know where from here, because the fuel is completely empty.
空っ風に笑う楽観主義が 生むはまさに難関
Optimism laughing in the dry wind only breeds difficulties.
一人になりたくても人だらけ 避けたくだらん耳も一苦労なわけ
Even if I want to be alone, it's crowded. Tuning out the nonsense is hard work.
惹かれたくないサレンダーピープル でもどこいたってピポピポピポ
I don't want to be drawn to those surrender people, but wherever I go, there are sirens.
黄信号ずっと進行
A yellow light, always moving forward,
死亡した先はあることレッドカードで
even if death awaits with a red card.
ははっ、足りない何だった？ Come on!
Haha, what was missing? Come on!
よりどり緑ってさっき言ったろ？
I told you earlier, it's full of choices, right?
あれこれ心が荒立つくらい
My heart is rough with all these things,
言いたかったことが晴天の霹靂
and what I wanted to say came out of the blue.
しかし悔しさで黒く燃える腹ん中
But inside, my gut burns black with regret.
燃やせ！燃やせ！燃やせ！
Burn it! Burn it! Burn it!
燃やす闘志 その手少し ぶっ壊し通しようもないままが自分なんだ
Burning this fighting spirit, breaking it all, my helpless self is who I am!
Get up, stand up, こっから始まんだ
Get up, stand up, it starts from here!
いつかの闘志 持って少し 夢と添い遂げられるはずんだ
Carrying that old fighting spirit, I should be able to live out my dreams.
Get up, stand up, こっから、こっから始まんだ
Get up, stand up, it starts from here, right here!
One, two, three, let's go!
Check check to the bridge!
俺 悪くない 何も間違ってない
I did nothing wrong, I made no mistake.
自分じゃない 何かのせいにしたい
I'm not the one, I want to blame it on something else.
天才じゃないの だっせ分かんなさい
I'm no genius, so understand my uncoolness.
これ フィクションじゃない よく見なさい
This is not fiction, take a good look.
天分の才などない でも...
I have no natural talent, but...
やめられない みたい
I just can't seem to stop.
あたしゃ阿呆か 馬鹿みたい
Am I a fool? Like an idiot.
天才
Genius!
こっから
From here!
燃える未来
A burning future!
メラメラ まだまだ
Blazing hot, don't write yourself off yet!
自分で決めつけんな
Find your limit, in your own world.
限界 探せよ お前ら
Limit! Find it! Everyone's...
世界
...world!
本当の自分なんていやしねえよ
There's no such thing as a "true self" anyway.
高くなきゃダメ 低くてもダメ
It's no good high, it's no good low,
と思い込んでることこそが
assuming that itself is the problem.
好きこそものの上手なれ
What one likes, one will do well.
次こそ吼える根比べ
Next up is a contest of who barks louder.
I can be so one way, so I know I know
このブレーキを壊したいの したいの
I want to break this brake, I really do.
あ、四の五の言わずに動け
Ah, stop making excuses and move.
道なき道ほど進め
Advance further on the pathless road.
どの叱咤も嫉妬なら燃料
If any scolding is just jealousy, it's fuel.
Let it fire!
燃やすこの闘志 その鉄格子 ぶち壊し
Burn this fighting spirit, break down that iron grid.
どうしようもないままが自分なんだ
Being helpless is exactly who I am.
こっから 始まんだ
It starts from here!
いつかの童心 持ってただろうし 夢と
You probably still have that childhood heart, and your dream...
相思相愛になれるはずんだ
...and you are meant to be mutually in love.
こっから
From here...
こっから始まんだ|こっから始まんだ
...it starts from right here!
Yeah! 1234 順番通り
Yeah! 1, 2, 3, 4, in order,
いってないだけで予定通り
just haven't said it, but all on schedule.
rollin' rollin' 転がってけ
Rollin' rollin', keep on rolling,
よりどりみどりの一生
a life full of endless choices.
1234 順番通り
1, 2, 3, 4, in order,
いってないだけで予定通り
just haven't said it, but all on schedule.
rollin' rollin' 転がってけ
Rollin' rollin', keep on rolling,
こっから始まんだ
it starts from here!
数年後
- a few years later -
A few years later
Ha, ha, ha...
I can't see what's behind those eyes
Just wait, talk a little before they're right
誰かの理想像に
To someone else's ideal image,
耳を傾けてしまったの
I ended up listening to it.
I can't take it back no more
I guess it's too late to call it off
感情の無い世界に溺れてさ
Drowning in a world with no emotions.
Tell me who I'm supposed to be
I'm lost without your honesty
I'm stuck between yes and no
Don't let me down
This is what you came for
狂ったように舞いな 舞いな
Dance like you're going crazy, crazy!
Said you wanna be a Superstar
Show me you won't break and fall apart
Take me higher, higher!
何かを言おうとして
Trying to say something,
間違い探しのスタート合図
the starting signal for a spot-the-difference game.
Why's everybody's eyes on me?
慣れてしまうものね 視線の的
I guess I've gotten used to being the target of their gaze.
I can't take it back no more
I guess it's too late to call it off
感じるプレッシャーは押し殺してさ
Suppressing the pressure that I feel.
Tell me who I'm supposed to be
I'm lost without your honesty
いい子気取りじゃ no no no
Acting like a good kid? No, no, no.
Don't let me down
This is what you came for
狂ったように舞いな 舞いな
Dance like you're going crazy, crazy!
Said you wanna be a Superstar
Show me you won't break and fall apart
Take me higher, higher!
Said you wanna be a Superstar
So show me what you got
I can't take it back no more
I guess it's too late to call it off
感情の無い世界に溺れてさ
Drowning in a world with no emotions.
Tell me who I'm supposed to be
I'm lost without your honesty
I'm stuck between yes and no
Don't let me down
This is what you came for
狂ったように舞いな 舞いな
Dance like you're going crazy, crazy!
Said you wanna be a Superstar
Show me you won't break and fall apart
La la la la la...
Take me higher, higher!
Show me your...
わー！皆さん！ありがとう！
Wow! Everyone! Thank you!
仲間と励まし合って、
We encouraged each other as comrades...
みんなから勇気をもらって、
...received courage from everyone...
こうしてステージに立って、たくさんの人の前でパフォーマンスすることができました！ありがとうございます！
...and were able to stand on stage like this and perform in front of so many people! Thank you so much!
そして！なんと！Xトレンド1位！ありがとうございます！
And also! Somehow! We trended #1 on X! Thank you so much!
そして、チャンネル登録者様も120万人様にいったみたいで、本当にありがとうございます！
And also, it seems we reached 1.2 million subscribers! Thank you so very much!
わー！嬉しい！
Yay! I'm so happy!
こうしてね、夢追いかけて、上京して、こう、たくさんの人のスターになることができました！轟はじめです！
Like this, chasing my dream, moving to Tokyo... I was able to become a star for so many people! I'm Todoroki Hajime!
でもね、この物語を作るにあたって、たくさんの素敵なアーティストさんの楽曲をお借りして、作ることができたので、本当にありがとうございました。
But you know, in making this story, we borrowed songs from many wonderful artists to make it happen, so thank you so very much.
はじめも、曲をたくさん作れるように、頑張ります！
Hajime will also do her best to make many songs!
そして、これがはじめの100万人記念の新衣装になります！
And this is Hajime's new outfit for the 1 million milestone!
衣装の名前は「ブラッドコード」衣装です。市原達矢様に仕立てていただきました。
The name of this outfit is "Blood Code". It was designed and tailored by Ichihara Tatsuya-sama!
これも、みなさんが応援してくれたおかげです。ありがとうございます！
This is also thanks to everyone supporting me. Thank you!
で、今回の新衣装ね、髪がロング！そして、足がなんかすごく長く見えるデザインで、わざとアシンメトリーな見え方になってます。
And for this new outfit, the hair is long! Also, the legs are designed to look very long, making it look asymmetrical on purpose.
皆、なんかおかしくない？
Doesn't something seem off to everyone?
ぴょこぴょこがない？嘘だ！そんなバカな！そんなバカな！ぴょこぴょこがないだって？
There are no hair wiggles? No way! That's impossible! That's impossible! No hair wiggles?
うわ、嘘です！ぴょこぴょこもあります！
Whoa, just kidding! I have hair wiggles too!
まぁ、ぴょこぴょこないと脳みそ出ちゃうからね、必要だよね。
Well, without the wiggles, my brains would spill out, so they are necessary.
で、あと、ジャケットも脱げます！ほら！セクシー？こうして、この後のメン限で紹介するので、気になる方は見に来てください。
Also, I can take off the jacket! See! Sexy? I'll introduce it in the members-only stream after this, so please come watch!
えー、続いてなんと、新曲を披露しようと思います！
And next, I'm going to perform a new song!
皆さん、盛り上がる準備、できてますか？
Everyone, are you ready to get excited?
ロング可愛い？ありがとう！
Long hair is cute? Thank you!
とてもね、格好良くて、なんかセクシーな感じの曲になってるので、ぜひ聴いてください！それでは行きます！「Deep Dive」
It's a very cool and somewhat sexy song, so please listen to it! Here we go! "Deep Dive".
[新曲：Deep Dive]
[New Song: Deep Dive]
Midnight 今夜は with my girlies
Midnight tonight with my girlies
Baby 救ってあげるよ Let's get party
Baby, I'll save you, let's get the party started
頭から爪先まで
From head to toe...
Okay my ladies, I need you to show me
Wow magic gorgeous dance, you look so badass
Scream, scream, scream and shout, hey!
Hurry up now
Me and my girls, me and my girls
見てよ We are amazing, we are so amazing
Look, we are amazing, we are so amazing
Me and my girls, me and my girls, ごく自然
Me and my girls, me and my girls, so natural
Yes, I'm so hot, look
Dive, let's deep dive, I wanna deep dive
Dive, your deep dive
Dive, your deep dive, let's get it out of control
Girl, you're looking like that girl, 間違いなく so hot
Girl, you're looking like that girl, definitely so hot
My sunny queen, hot queen, hot queen
Girl, you're looking like that girl, 間違いなく so hot
Girl, you're looking like that girl, definitely so hot
My sunny queen, hot queen, hot queen
First class, the star girl
The minimum, the hardcore
眩しいほど so shiny, mask off して I'm burning
So shiny it's blinding, taking off my mask, I'm burning
髪なびかせて my body, ooh la la ooh la la
With my hair fluttering, my body, ooh la la ooh la la
視線をコントロール out of my mind
Controlling your gaze, out of my mind
誰かのコピーコピー I don't need anymore
A copy of someone else, I don't need that anymore
Wow magic gorgeous dance, you look so badass
Gimme, gimme show time, hey!
Gimme, gimme showtime, hey!
Turn it up now, make up!
Are you ready? Are you ready? Let it, let it go!
Me and my girls, me and my girls
We gotta, we gotta, we gotta, we gotta, we gotta...
Crazy, crazy, crazy!
Let's get back to beat
You're so hot, queen!
Dive, let's deep dive. I want to deep dive.
Dive, deep dive. Hey! Hey! Hey!
Dive, deep dive. Let's get it on, let's get it on!
Girl, you look like that girl
街をそう闊歩、まさにクイーン
Strutting through the streets like a true queen
Hot queen, hot queen!
Girl, you look like that girl
街をそう闊歩、まさにクイーン
Strutting through the streets like a true queen
Hot queen, hot queen!
はい！ということで、生誕グッズが出ました！
All right! With that, my birthday merchandise is out!
と、と、轟はじめ誕生日記念2026...
Todoroki Hajime Birthday Celebration 2026...
フルセットはこんな感じです！
This is what the Full Set looks like!
ひとつずつ紹介していきます！
I'll introduce them one by one!
まず1つ目！
First one!
ぶんぶん番長アクリルスタンド！
The Bunbun Bancho Acrylic Stand!
イラストは、A5き先生に描いていただきました！
The illustration was drawn by Azuki-sensei!
台座がふたつあるので、座っている風にも、普通のスタンドとしても使えます！
With two bases, you can display her sitting or as a regular stand!
怒っているのがポイントです！
Her angry expression is the key point!
2つ目は！
Second one!
はじめとお揃いチョーカー！
Matching Choker with Hajime!
はじめの新衣装とお揃いのチョーカーです！
It's a choker matching Hajime's new outfit!
星のチャームが可愛い！
The star charm is so cute!
首のサイズが合わないよという方は、バッグなどに付けてください！
If it doesn't fit your neck, please attach it to your bag instead!
3つ目は！
Third one!
BANCHOジャージ！
The BANCHO Track Jacket!
裏面のイラストはおもちチャウダーちゃんに描いていただきました！
The back illustration was drawn by Omochi Chowder-chan!
表面は刺繍になってます！
The front design is embroidered!
スバル先輩の生地がとても良かったので、同じのにしていただきました！
Subaru-senpai's jacket fabric was so good, so I got the same one!
最後！ぬいぐるみキーホルダー ブラックオーロラ衣装ver.！
Lastly! Plushie Keyring (Black Aurora Outfit Ver.)!
初めて出した人気のぬいぐるみの、新衣装バージョンです！
It's a new outfit version of the popular plushie we first released!
あの時買えなかったよという方、ぜひお迎えしてください！
If you couldn't get it back then, please take this chance to get her!
そして、フルセット特典はこちら！
And here is the Full Set bonus!
今回のライブのチケット風カード！
A concert ticket-style card for this live!
全員に直筆サイン書かせていただきます！
I will hand-sign every single one of them!
去年のね、ライブでたくさんグッズを買っていただいたおかげで、
Thanks to everyone buying so much merch at last year's live,
今年もこんなに力を入れることができました！ありがとうございます！
I was able to put so much effort into it again this year! Thank you!
今回のライブも楽しんでいただくのはもちろん、
Of course, I hope you enjoy today's live,
記念にグッズもお迎えしていただけると、今後の励みになります！
but getting the commemorative merch would also really encourage me!
よろしくお願いします！
Thank you so much!
以上、グッズ紹介でした！
That's all for the merch introduction!
お待たせしました！
Thank you for waiting!
このあとはラストスパート！
Up next is the last spurt!
一緒に盛り上がっていってください！いきますよ！
Let's get hyped up together! Here we go!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
Oh!
Wow マジ gorgeous, thanks
Wow, you're seriously gorgeous, thanks!
You look so badass
Scream, scream, scream and shout ay
Wow マジ gorgeous, thanks
Wow, you're seriously gorgeous, thanks!
You look so badass
Scream, scream, scream and shout ay
Turn it up now let go
Turn it up now, let's go!
Me and my girls, me and my girls
見てよ we're amazing, we are so amazing
Look, we're amazing, we are so amazing!
Me and my girls, me and my girls
ここから dive
Diving from right here...
Yes, I'm a hot queen
Dive, let's deep dive, I wanna deep dive
みんな！ありがとう！
Everyone! Thank you!
はあ、みんなありがとうございました！
Phew, thank you so much, everyone!
それでは、今回のライブに携わってくださった方をご紹介していきたいと思います！
Now, I'd like to introduce the people who helped out with this live concert!
まずはダンサー！夢にゃん！
First, the dancers! Yumenyan!
で、ちおりゃん！
And Chiorian!
う、みなみゃん！
And Minamiyan!
と、そら！
And Sora!
ありがとう！そして
Thank you! And also...
この場にはいないんですけど、振付師のMiU Kinoshita先生！
Though they aren't here right now, our choreographer MiU Kinoshita-sensei!
タップのAYAKA先生！
Tap dance instructor AYAKA-sensei!
で、ポッピンのTO-Y先生！
And pop dance instructor TO-Y-sensei!
ダンス監修、YUKA先生！
Dance supervisor YUKA-sensei!
ボーカル監修、MARIA先生！
Vocal supervisor MARIA-sensei!
そしてゲストにお越しいただきました
And we also had special guests join us...
胡桃ちよちゃん！
Kurumi Chiyo-chan!
ハコトベーンズちゃん！
Hakotobeanzu-chan!
伊咲りおなちゃん！
Izaki Riona-chan!
水宮つうちゃん！
Mizumiya Tsuu-chan!
本当にありがとうございました！
Thank you all so much!
そして、今見えない中で稼働してくださってるスタッフの皆さん！
And to all the staff working hard behind the scenes where we can't see!
そして、はじめの目の前にいてくれてる、観てくれた皆様、本当にありがとうございました！
And to everyone right here in front of Hajime, and everyone who watched, thank you so much!
それでは、ちょっと新曲について詳しくご紹介したいなと思います！改めてタイトルは、Deep Dive！
Now, I'd like to share some details about my new song! Once again, the title is \"Deep Dive\"!
はい、MV公開はこの配信のすぐ後です！
Yes, the MV will be released right after this stream!
音源リリースは本日24時からになります！
The audio track will be released starting tonight at 24:00!
皆さんたくさん聴いていただけると嬉しいです！
I hope you all listen to it a lot!
さあ、それではここで重大発表をいきたいと思います！
Now, I'd like to make a major announcement!
こちらの動画をご覧ください！
Please take a look at this video!
轟はじめ × FILA
Todoroki Hajime x FILA
コラボ決定!!
Collaboration Decided!!
COMING SOON!!
わあ、凄い！この度、はじめとFILAさんのコラボが決定しました！
Wow, amazing! This time, a collaboration between Hajime and FILA has been decided!
うわ、嬉しい！ありがとうございます！
Oh, I'm so happy! Thank you so much!
そして、なんとスニーカーを含むアパレルをプロデュースさせていただきました！
And, what's more, I got to produce apparel including sneakers!
やったー！
Yay!
はじめっぽいカラーリングを取り入れながら、男性でも女性でも似合うように意識してデザインしてみました！
While incorporating colors that feel like Hajime, I designed them focusing on making them look good on both men and women!
一足目、はじめのこだわりを詰め込んだスニーカーにしていくので、続報を楽しみに待っていてください！
For the first pair, I'll be packing them with Hajime's personal touches, so please look forward to more updates!
そして、今回なんとあのスニーカーだけじゃなくてですね、ジャージとTシャツとキャップもプロデュースしちゃいました！
And, not only the sneakers this time, but I also produced jerseys, T-shirts, and caps!
さらにコラボに当たって、オリジナルのコラボロゴをFILAさんと作りました！ドドン！
Furthermore, for this collaboration, I created an original collab logo with FILA! Ta-da!
わあ、可愛い！
Wow, so cute!
実はこのね、ロゴFILAさんと一緒に打ち合わせをして考えました、はじめ。
Actually, Hajime held meetings with FILA to come up with this logo.
あ、こう、こういう感じにね、実際にこう手書きをしながら打ち合わせをして、どの色いいかなって、いろんな色味を出してもらって、これにしました！
Yes, we had meetings while doing hand-drawings like this, discussing which colors would look best, and they showed me various color palettes to choose from before we settled on this!
ひと目でね、もうはじめだってわかる、こう、ミニ番長のシルエットがいいかなと思って入れてみました！
I thought it'd be great to have a silhouette of Mini Bancho so you can recognize it's Hajime at a glance, so we put it in!
このロゴがね、コラボの商品にも付きます！楽しみにしてほしいにゃあ！
This logo will also be on the collaboration products! Please look forward to it!
実はね、アパレル以外にもFILAさんとのコラボ商品が出ますので、皆さん詳細な情報が出るの、ぜひお楽しみに、お待ちください！
Actually, besides apparel, there will be other collaboration products with FILA, so please look forward to the detailed information when it comes out!
この後ですね、メンバー限定アンコールライブ、21時15分からありますし、
After this, there will be a members-only encore live starting at 21:15,
この新曲についてもいろいろ詳しく見ていければと思いますので、ぜひまだの方はチャンネル登録と通知をオンにしてメンバーも入っていただけると、アンコールも一緒に楽しめてハッピーだなと思います！
I also want to go over details about the new song with you all, so if you haven't yet, please subscribe, turn on notifications, and join the membership. We can enjoy the encore together and be happy!
おさらいをすると、新曲MVこの後すぐ公開、ええ、21時からグッズ販売、21時15分からアンコールライブ、24時新曲音源リリースです！
To recap: the new song's MV is released right after this, merchandise sales start at 21:00, the encore live is at 21:15, and the new song's audio track releases at 24:00!
ありがとうにゃん！
Thank you!
それでは、メンバー限定アンコールライブでお会いしましょう！バイバーイ！
Well then, let's meet at the members-only encore live! Bye-bye!
いっぱいコメントありがとう！嬉しかった！
Thank you for all the comments! I was so happy!
あ、ありがとう
Ah, thank you!